cometdocs.com 2019-05-01

# Privacy Policy | Cometdocs

(Effective as of June 5th, 2018)

Cometdocs.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy, as a visitor of our website and as a user of our services, is protected.

Our privacy policy explains all information that we record about you. It demonstrates the conditions under which we may process any information that we collect from you, or that you provide to us. Your personal data will not be used for any unintended purpose and it will not accidentally fall into the hands of third parties.

Our privacy policy complies with UK law accordingly implemented, including that required by the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

It is our legal obligation to notify you about your rights and our duties to you regarding the processing and controlling your personal data. We do this now, by requesting that you read the information that is provided at the website www.knowyourprivacyrights.org.

##  Use of Personal Information

We will not share, sell, lease, disclose, transfer, transmit or rent any personal information you submit through the Cometdocs.com website without your consent.

Below are described the categories of information we collect from and about you when you use our services:

-Contact information-  
When you create an account on Cometdocs, purchase a subscription from us, or otherwise agree to our terms and conditions, a contract is formed between you and us. With the aim to perform our obligations that are under the contract, we have to process your information including your full name and email address. Additionally, we may ask you for personal information at other times, such as when you contact our support team, or communicate with Cometdocs in any other way.

-Registration through integrated sign-up services-  
If you register through Facebook, Google, or Microsoft mail, we may collect your personal information that is already correlated with your account on mentioned integrated services.

We will continue to process your personal information until the contract between us ends or is terminated by either party under the terms of the contract.

In certain occasions when there is no contract between us, such as when you browse our website or ask us to provide you more information about our business, you give your consent to us to process your information. By asking you to agree to our use of cookies we are asking you for your explicit consent to process such information.

You may withdraw your consent at any time by emailing us at  
compliance@cometdocs.com.

##  Emails addresses

We will email you only for service related purposes: 1. to send you a converted/transferred/shared file, 2. inform you about the status of a conversion/transfer/sharing process and 3. to inform you about the status of your account and your files. Occasionally, we might send you newest releases and news about Cometdocs, if you are a registered user.

Your email is never going to be rented or sold to a third party. Registered users can manage their email notifications by going to Account - Settings in their account.

Each message will include instructions on how to unsubscribe from future mailings.

##  Retention of Personal Information

Except as otherwise written in this privacy policy, we keep your personal information only for as long as it is necessary to provide you with the services you have requested, to comply with the law, including for the period requested by our tax authorities, to support a claim or defence in court.

##  Access to your personal information

You have a right to review or update your personal information any time by logging into your Cometdocs account. If you need a copy of any information that is not available on the website, send us an email at compliance@cometdocs.com. Once we receive your request, we will inform you when we can give the information and whether we require any fee for that matter.

##  Cookies

Cometdocs.com might put a cookie on your website. A website cookie is a small piece of information that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies can be deleted from your browser. You can still access Cometdocs.com if you setup your browser to not accept cookies. Cometdocs.com cookies don't collect personally identifiable information. We only use this information for statistical analysis of visits and to improve the quality of services we offer.

##  Security

We apply security practices in order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure. While being fully committed to maintaining a high level of security here at Cometdocs, please be aware of the fact that there is a level of risk involved in any transmissions of data via the Internet. No transmission of data over the Internet can ever be guaranteed to be completely secure.

##  Handling uploaded and converted files

We store uploaded files to our server only temporarily for conversion purposes. When the conversion process ends, we delete those files from our servers automatically. The converted file is stored on our servers for 24 hours so that the user can download it. When a registered user converts a file, the file will remain on our servers until the user deletes it from within their own file manager.

There is no back-up of stored files. Contents of the files are not being monitored in any way by Cometdocs.com or any other third party. The content of the file is accessible via download link users receive in their email or in their File Manager if they are registered users.

##  Third parties

We will not share, rent, lease or sell any of your data to third parties. We might put advertising links on our website. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own. Cometdocs is not responsible for the advertiser's privacy policy.

##  Transfer and sharing of data

In the course of providing the Services data is transferred to and from servers located in the United States. By agreeing to Cometdocs's Terms of Service you accept the transfer of such data as is necessary to provide the Services. Data may be processed outside the European Union. We may also use outsourced services in countries that are not in the European Union. Data obtained within the UK or any other country could be processed outside the European Union.

The processor belong to the same corporate group as our business and abides by the same binding corporate rules regarding data processing. Data protection clauses in our contracts with data processors include transfer clauses written by or approved by a supervisory authority in the European Union.

##  Use of site by children

We do not sell services to children, nor do we market to children. If you are under 18, you may use our website only with consent from a parent or guardian Cometdocs collects data about all users and visitors regardless of age, and we anticipate that some of those users and visitors will be children.

##  Exceptional Disclosures

We may disclose your personal information only in the case where required by law or if we receive former legal process with respect to a certain document or user of our service.

##  Changes in our privacy policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post changes to this page. This policy was last modified on 05/30/2018. We advise you to print this version of our privacy policy because the terms that apply to you are those you found here on our website on the day you visited it.

##  Terms and conditions

Please visit our Terms and Conditions section related to the use of this website.  
http://www.cometdocs.com/tos.htm

If you have questions about our privacy policy, please send an email to 

##  Compliance with the law

Our privacy policy complies with the law of every country or legal jurisdiction in which we do business. If you think it fails to satisfy the law of your jurisdiction, we would like to hear from you.
